# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### **Cactus Communications**

Sr. Software Engineer Jun 2020 - Present Python Developer May 2018 - Jun 2020

- Worked on projects in the domain of ML,DL and big data
- Created end-to-end machine learning pipelines in production environment using cloud infrastructure in a fault tolerant and cost-effective manner

# **SKILLS**

ML, DL, NLP, image processing, distributed training, big data

AWS, GCP, Azure, EC2, ECS, S3, EMR, Lambda, Redshift, Kinesis, Step functions etc

### **EDUCATION**

NMIMS University
Bachelor in Technology, Computer
Jun 2014 - May 2018

# JINAM SHAH

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/jinamshah/ E-mail: hi@jinamshah.com

#### **PROFILE**

I am a developer with expertise in creating products using ML,DL,big data in an unprecedented manner and also scaling them using cloud infrastructure. I have an experience working in all stages of a ML/DL pipeline (data collection, modeling, deploying, scaling etc.) and can do so in a highly cost-efficient manner.

### **PROJECTS**

- Subject area detector: ensemble of DL and ML models performing document classification for over 1500 classes deployed in serverless architecture
- ML model for emergency response identification from text
- Ethical image checker: image classifier for determining ethical compliance of images added in research papers recognizing faces, tattoos, birthmarks, face drawings etc, deployed using serverless architecture
- Distributed training on cloud-based infrastructure for custom deep learning model reducing time to train by 2 times at approximately the same cost

...more on github: https://github.com/jinamshah

## COURSES/CERTIFICATIONS

- Kaggle Introduction to ML, Intermediate ML, Feature Engineering
- Udacity AWS Machine learning foundations, Spark